{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": " 36x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-6)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-6x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": " 25x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n5^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "343x / 16", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(7^3/4^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(343 / 16)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^3 / (4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["100 / (343x)"], "answer": "100 / 343x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(10^2/7^3)x^(2 - 3)\n(100 / 343)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^2 / (7x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["100 / (343x)"], "answer": "216x^5", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(1^2 * 6^3)x^(2 + 3)\n(1 * 216)x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\nx^2 * (6x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["100 / (343x)"], "answer": "576x^6", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(6^2 * 2^4)x^(2 + 4)\n(36 * 16)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(6x)^2 * (2x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["100 / (343x)"], "answer": " x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-1)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["100 / (343x)"], "answer": "343x^3", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(7^6/7^3)x^(6 - 3)\n(117649 / 343)x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^6 / (7x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "36 / x^3", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(6^2/1^5)x^(2 - 5)\n(36 / 1)x^-3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(6x)^2 / x^5", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "64x^13", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(1^7 * 2^6)x^(7 + 6)\n(1 * 64)x^13\n", "question": "Simplify:\nx^7 * (2x)^6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "4608x^5", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(8^3 * -3^2)x^(3 + 2)\n(512 * 9)x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(8x)^3 * (-3x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "125x^3", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(5^6/5^3)x^(6 - 3)\n(15625 / 125)x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^6 / (5x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": " 16x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-4)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "x / 4", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(2^4/4^3)x^(4 - 3)\n(16 / 64)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x)^4 / (4x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": " 36x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-6)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-6x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "64x / 81", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(4^3/9^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(64 / 81)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^3 / (9x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": " 625x^4", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n5^4 * x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "81x^2", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(9^5/9^3)x^(5 - 3)\n(59049 / 729)x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(9x)^5 / (9x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "40x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(10^3/5^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(1000 / 25)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^3 / (5x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "512x^5", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(4^4 * 2)x^(4 + 1)\n(256 * 2)x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^4 * 2x", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "5625x^6", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(5^4 * -3^2)x^(4 + 2)\n(625 * 9)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^4 * (-3x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["36 / (x^3)", "36 / (x^3)"], "answer": "10x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(10^3/10^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(1000 / 100)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^3 / (10x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (5x)"], "answer": "1 / 5x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(5^3/5^4)x^(3 - 4)\n(125 / 625)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^3 / (5x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (2x)"], "answer": "1 / 2x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(2^3/2^4)x^(3 - 4)\n(8 / 16)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x)^3 / (2x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (2x)"], "answer": "729x^6", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-3^2 * 3^4)x^(2 + 4)\n(9 * 81)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-3x)^2 * (3x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (2x)"], "answer": "1225x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-7^2 * -5^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(49 * 25)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-7x)^2 * (-5x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (2x)"], "answer": "1600x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-8^2 * 5^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(64 * 25)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-8x)^2 * (5x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (2x)"], "answer": "64x^13", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(2^6 * 1^7)x^(6 + 7)\n(64 * 1)x^13\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x)^6 * x^7", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["49 / (625x^2)"], "answer": "49 / 625x^2", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(7^2/5^4)x^(2 - 4)\n(49 / 625)x^-2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^2 / (5x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "1 / 3x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(3^2/3^3)x^(2 - 3)\n(9 / 27)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x)^2 / (3x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "9x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(9^3/9^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(729 / 81)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(9x)^3 / (9x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "1024x^10", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(2^4 * 2^6)x^(4 + 6)\n(16 * 64)x^10\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x)^4 * (2x)^6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "-243x^6", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(3^5 * -1)x^(5 + 1)\n(243 * -1)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x)^5 * -x", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "1764x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(7^2 * 6^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(49 * 36)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^2 * (6x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "1 / 3x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(3^3/3^4)x^(3 - 4)\n(27 / 81)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x)^3 / (3x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": " 27x^3", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n3^3 * x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "3136x^5", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(4^3 * 7^2)x^(3 + 2)\n(64 * 49)x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^3 * (7x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": " 100x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n10^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": " 100x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-10)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-10x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "729x / 4", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(9^3/2^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(729 / 4)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(9x)^3 / (2x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "1225x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-5^2 * -7^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(25 * 49)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-5x)^2 * (-7x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "49x^8", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-7^2 * 1^6)x^(2 + 6)\n(49 * 1)x^8\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-7x)^2 * x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "81x^6", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-1^2 * 3^4)x^(2 + 4)\n(1 * 81)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-x)^2 * (3x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "729x / 64", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(9^3/8^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(729 / 64)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(9x)^3 / (8x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "5625x^6", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-3^2 * 5^4)x^(2 + 4)\n(9 * 625)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-3x)^2 * (5x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": " 343x^3", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n7^3 * x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (3x)"], "answer": "6x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(6^3/6^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(216 / 36)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(6x)^3 / (6x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "1 / 10x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(10^2/10^3)x^(2 - 3)\n(100 / 1000)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^2 / (10x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-1)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 1000x^3", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n10^3 * x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 49x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n7^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": "81 / 512x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(9^2/8^3)x^(2 - 3)\n(81 / 512)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(9x)^2 / (8x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": "144x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-4^2 * 3^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(16 * 9)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-4x)^2 * (3x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": " 512x^3", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n8^3 * x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(8x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": "576x^5", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(4^3 * 3^2)x^(3 + 2)\n(64 * 9)x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^3 * (3x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": " 243x^5", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n3^5 * x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x)^5", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": "49x^2", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(7^4/7^2)x^(4 - 2)\n(2401 / 49)x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^4 / (7x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": "256x^6", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(2^4 * 4^2)x^(4 + 2)\n(16 * 16)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x)^4 * (4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": " 729x^3", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n9^3 * x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(9x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["81 / (512x)"], "answer": " 8x^3", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n2^3 * x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "1 / 4x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(4^3/4^4)x^(3 - 4)\n(64 / 256)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^3 / (4x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": " 64x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n8^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(8x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "225x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(5^2 * -3^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(25 * 9)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^2 * (-3x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "324x^6", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(3^4 * -2^2)x^(4 + 2)\n(81 * 4)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x)^4 * (-2x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": " 81x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n9^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(9x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "1 / 4x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(4^3/4^4)x^(3 - 4)\n(64 / 256)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^3 / (4x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "3087x^5", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(7^3 * 3^2)x^(3 + 2)\n(343 * 9)x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^3 * (3x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": " 16x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n4^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": " 16x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n4^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "3136x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(7^2 * -8^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(49 * 64)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(7x)^2 * (-8x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "256x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-8^2 * -2^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(64 * 4)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-8x)^2 * (-2x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": " 16x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-4)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "10x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(10^3/10^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(1000 / 100)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^3 / (10x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": " 64x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-8)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-8x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": " 81x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-9)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-9x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": "432x^5", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(3^3 * 4^2)x^(3 + 2)\n(27 * 16)x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x)^3 * (4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (4x)"], "answer": " 32x^5", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n2^5 * x^5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x)^5", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["64 / (729x)"], "answer": "64 / 729x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(8^2/9^3)x^(2 - 3)\n(64 / 729)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(8x)^2 / (9x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["64 / (729x)"], "answer": " 25x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-5)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-5x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "1 / 10x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(10^2/10^3)x^(2 - 3)\n(100 / 1000)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^2 / (10x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "x^6 / 125", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(1^9/5^3)x^(9 - 3)\n(1 / 125)x^6\n", "question": "Simplify:\nx^9 / (5x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 36x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n6^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(6x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 4x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n2^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 216x^3", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n6^3 * x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(6x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 36x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n6^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(6x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "4x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(4^3/4^2)x^(3 - 2)\n(64 / 16)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^3 / (4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "16x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-2^2 * 2^2)x^(2 + 2)\n(4 * 4)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-2x)^2 * (2x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "10x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(10^4/10^3)x^(4 - 3)\n(10000 / 1000)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^4 / (10x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "-512x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by multiplying the two numbers and add the exponents.\n(-1 * 8^3)x^(1 + 3)\n(-1 * 512)x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-x * (8x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "x^3 / 1000", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(1^6/10^3)x^(6 - 3)\n(1 / 1000)x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\nx^6 / (10x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 16x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n4^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "4x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(4^4/4^3)x^(4 - 3)\n(256 / 64)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^4 / (4x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 625x^4", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n5^4 * x^4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "625x / 512", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(5^4/8^3)x^(4 - 3)\n(625 / 512)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^4 / (8x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": "5x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(5^4/5^3)x^(4 - 3)\n(625 / 125)x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(5x)^4 / (5x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (10x)"], "answer": " 9x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n(-3)^2 * x^2\nA negative number raised to an even power is a positive number.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(-3x)^2", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["729 / (625x)"], "answer": "729 / 625x", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(9^3/5^4)x^(3 - 4)\n(729 / 625)x^-1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(9x)^3 / (5x)^4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (x^4)", "1 / (x^4)"], "answer": "1 / x^4", "explanation": "Simplify by dividing the two numbers and subtracting the exponents.\n(1^2/1^6)x^(2 - 6)\n(1 / 1)x^-4\n", "question": "Simplify:\nx^2 / x^6", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (x^4)", "1 / (x^4)"], "answer": " 1000x^3", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n10^3 * x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(10x)^3", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["1 / (x^4)", "1 / (x^4)"], "answer": " 16x^2", "explanation": "Distribute the exponent through the parenthesis.\n4^2 * x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^2", "type": "text"}
]}